hi I'm Shakti Shilpa from the yoga space
and today we are going to see how to do
child's pose or balasana sitting on your
heels
slowly move on to a table
exhale and lower the hips to the heels
[Music]
and forward on the flow have the knees
together or if you're more comfortable
spread the knees slightly apart
[Music]
the arms can be overhead with your palms
on the floor
palms office can be stacked under the
forehead
[Music]
our arms can be alongside the body with
palms up
[Music]
if you feel that your knee is hurting or
if you're unable to sit on your heels
you can keep a bolster or blanket
between your legs and then do the pose
[Music]
or if the top of the foot is stretching
too much and the bolster can be placed
just below your feet
remember that this is a restoration
calming pause so fine what works best
for you to relax breathe slowly and
deeply pressing the belly against the
thighs on the inhale breathe and hold
for 4 to 12 breaths
[Music]
to release place the palms under your
shoulders and slowly inhale up to a
seated position
you